socialclerks.com 2014-03-30

# SocialClerks - Free Twitter Followers, Facebook Likes and more

This Policy applies as to all products and services provided by SocialClerks the owner and provider of SocialClerks, and yourself the User of SocialClerks. This Policy applies to our use of any and all Data collected by us in relation to your use of SocialClerks and any Services or Systems therein.

**1\. Definitions and Interpretation**

In this Policy the following terms shall have the following meanings:

" **Account** " means collectively the personal information, payment information and credentials used by Users to access material and / or any communications System on SocialClerks;

" **Content** " means any text, graphics, images, audio, video, software, data compilations and any other form of information capable of being stored in a computer that appears on or forms part of SocialClerks;

" **Cookie** " means a small text file placed on your computer by SocialClerks when you visit certain parts of SocialClerks. This allows us to identify recurring visitors and to analyse their browsing habits within SocialClerks.

" **Data** " means collectively all information that you submit to SocialClerks. This includes, but is not limited to, Account details and information submitted using any of our Services or Systems;

" **Service** " means collectively any online facilities, tools, services or information that SocialClerksmakes available through SocialClerks either now or in the future;

" **System** " means any online communications infrastructure that SocialClerks makes available through SocialClerks either now or in the future. This includes, but is not limited to, web-based email, message boards, live chat facilities and email links;

" **User** " / " **Users** " means any third party that accesses SocialClerks and is not employed by SocialClerks and acting in the course of their employment; and

" **Member** " / " **Members** " means any third party that accesses SocialClerks and is not employed by SocialClerks and acting in the course of their employment; and

" **Web Site** " means the website that you are currently using (SocialClerk.net) and any sub-domains of this site unless expressly excluded by it`s own terms and conditions.

**2\. Data Collected**

Without limitation, any of the following Data may be collected:

2.1 name;

2.2 date of birth;

2.3 gender;

2.4 business industry;

2.5 contact information such as email addresses and telephone numbers;

2.6 demographic information such as post code, preferences and interests;

2.7 Cookie information (see clause 10 below);

2.8 financial information such as purchase history

2.9 IP address (automatically collected);

2.10 web browser type and version (automatically collected);

2.11 operating system (automatically collected);

2.12 a list of URLS starting with a referring site, your activity on SocialClerks, and the site you exit to (automatically collected); and

2.13 Twitter profile information provided to us through the Twitter API and your express permission;

2.14 Facebook profile information provided to us through the Facebook API and your express permission;

2.15 Youtube profile information provided to us through the YouTube API and your express permission;

2.16 Website profile information;

2.17 Online social connections made or received by you through SocialClerks.

**3\. Our Use of Data**

3.1 Any personal Data you submit will be retained by SocialClerks for as long as you use the Services and Systems provided on SocialClerks. Data that you may submit through any communications System that we may provide may be retained for a longer period.

3.2 Unless we are obliged or permitted by law to do so, and subject to Clause 4, your Data will not be disclosed to third parties.

3.3 All personal Data is stored securely in accordance with the principles of the Data Protection Act 1998. Fore more details on security, see clause 9 below.

3.4 Any or all of the above Data may be required by us from time to time in order to provide you with the best possible service and experience when using our Web Site. Specifically, Data may be used by us for the following reasons:

3.4.1 internal record keeping;

3.4.2 improvement of our products / services;

3.4.3 transmission by email of promotional materials that may be of interest to you;

3.4.4 contact for market research purposes which may be done using email, telephone, fax or mail. Such information may be used to customise or update SocialClerks.

**4\. Third Party Web Sites and Services**

SocialClerks may, from time to time, employ the services of other parties for dealing with matters that may include, but are not limited to, payment handling, delivery of purchased items, search engine facilities, advertising and marketing. The providers of such services do have access to certain personal Data provided by Users of SocialClerks. Any Data used by such parties is used only to the extent required by them to perform the services that SocialClerks requests. Any use for other purposes is strictly prohibited. Furthermore, any Data that is processed by third parties must be processed within the terms of this Policy and in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998.

**5\. Changes of Business Ownership and Control**

5.1 SocialClerks may, from time to time, expand or reduce its business and this may involve the sale of certain divisions or the transfer of control of certain divisions to other parties. Data provided by Users will, where it is relevant to any division so transferred, be transferred along with that division and the new owner or newly controlling party will, under the terms of this Policy, be permitted to use the Data for the purposes for which it was supplied by you.

5.2 In the event that any Data submitted by Users will be transferred in such a manner, you will not be contacted in advance and informed of the changes.

**6\. Controlling Access to your Data**

6.1 Wherever you are required to submit Data, you will not be given options to restrict our use of that Data.

**7\. Your Right to Withhold Information**

7.1 You may access certain areas of SocialClerks without providing any Data at all. However, to use all Services and Systems available on SocialClerks you may be required to submit Account information or other Data.

7.2 You may restrict your internet browser's use of Cookies. For more information see clause 10.4 below.

**8\. Accessing your own Data**

8.1 You may access your Account at any time to view or amend the Data. You may need to modify or update your Data if your circumstances change. Additional Data as to your marketing preferences may also be stored and you may change this at any time.

8.2 You have the right to ask for a copy of your personal Data on payment of a small administrative fee.

**9\. Security**

9.1 Data security is of great importance to SocialClerks and to protect your Data we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure Data collected online.

**10\. Cookies**

10.1 SocialClerks may set and access Cookies on your computer.

10.2 A Cookie is a small file that resides on your computer's hard drive and often contains an anonymous unique identifier and is accessible only by SocialClerks that placed it there, not any other sites.

10.3 You may delete Cookies, however you may lose any information that enables you to access SocialClerks more quickly.

10.4 You can choose to enable or disable Cookies in your web browser. By default, your browser will accept Cookies, however this can be altered. For further details please consult the help menu in your browser. Disabling Cookies may prevent you from using the full range of Services available on SocialClerks.

**11\. Changes to this Policy**

SocialClerks reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy as we may deem necessary from time to time or as may be required by law. Any changes will be immediately posted on SocialClerks and you are deemed to have accepted the terms of the Policy on your first use of SocialClerks following the alterations.
